

Mugi Anandika, S.T

PERSONAL INFO

Date of Birth : June 11th, 1999

Address : Jalan Tirta 3 Rt 007 Rw 03 No.34. Duren

Sawit. Jakarta Timur. DKI Jakarta. 13440

Nationality / Gender : Indonesian / Male

Email : mugianandika12@gmail.com

Mobile Phone number: 085769178322

LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/mugi-anandika/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Word - SQL - Google Data Studie

Microsoft Excel
 Microsoft Visio
 Google Cloud Platform
 PL/SQL
 R Language
 HTML
 JavaScript

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia

Native Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency (TOEIC Score: 780. Accredited by ETS)

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Head of Liaison Officer Division April Graduation (2019)

Association of Engineering Physics Students ITB Prepared and synergized information related to graduation activities, as a liaison between graduates and LO staff.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Mentor Artificial Intelligence (AI) (2021)

Orbit Future Academy

Mentoring and monitoring progress related to artificial intelligence projects including:

maks detection, chatbot manner and detecting social distance

Reviewer Digital Innovation Challenge (2021)

Markoding

Assessing the products of a digital innovation competition in which 482 high school and junior high students competed

CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Intensive Bootcamp Data Analysis, MySkill
- Bootcamp Data Science, PT. Sharing Vision Indonesia
- ASEAN Data Science Explorers 2022, ASEAN Foundation
- Foundations: Data, Data, Everywhere, Google
- Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions, Google
- Introduction to Sql, DataCamp
- Data Mining: Concept and Implementation, diklatkerja
- E-Training: Project Management Skills, PT. Sinergi Daya Mitra

PROFILE

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, who graduated with a Bachelor of Engineering in Engineering Physics major.

I have worked on projects about data processing and machine learning. Having solid proficiency of Python, R, SqL and Google Data Studio software.

EDUCATION

Bandung Institute of Technology (ITB) (2017 - 2021)

Bachelor of Engineering in Engineering Physics GPA 3.55/4.0 (Cum laude) ABET Accreditation Relevant coursework: Introduction to Information Technology B, Mathematics IA & IIA, Engineering Mathematics I & II, Probability and Statistics, Engineering Computation, Engineering Data Science, Engineering Management, Engineering Ethics and Industrial Job Training.

TRAINING

MySkill.id (2022)

Google Data Studio
 Spark
 HTML
 JavaScript
 Full Stack Intensive Bootcamp Data Analysis
 The bootcamp takes 1 month, the materials including:
 Intro data analysis, Basic Statistics, Data Formatting and
 Cleansing, SQL, Python and Data Visualization.

PT. Sharing Vision Indonesia (2022)

Data Science Bootcamp

The bootcamp takes 2 months (80 hours), 11 quizzes, 15 hands-on projects and 1 final project.

- Top 3 best participants in final project bootcamp.
- Learn Data Science and Machine Learning algorithm such as Basic python, Probability and Statistics, EDA, Data Preprocessing, Supervised and unsupervised machine learning, forecasting, SQL and Introduction to Deep Learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Engineer Analytics

(Oct 2022 - Oct 2023)

Bank Raya Indonesia, Jakarta

- Collaborate with data scientists and analysis on several projects.
- Extract Transform Load operations known as the ETL process.
- Building data architectures that meet the business requirements.

Internship as Data Scientist (Jun 2020 - Sep 2020)

PT. Indonesia Power, Jakarta

- Cleansing data from database using jupyter notebook
- Using classification techniques to detect outliers in data
- Creating a predictive maintenance model algorithm using the Python programming language.

PROJECTS

(https://github.com/mugianandika)

- Final Project Bootcamp Data Science
- Predictive Maintenance on Induced Draft Fans and Primary Air Fans Using a Classification Technique and an Artificial Neural Network (ANN) Model
- Anomaly Detection and Condition Monitoring Using Machine Learning Methods

AWARD

- Honorable Mention in Advantech AloT InnoWorks, organized by PT. Advantech International (June 2021)
- Silver award in Mathematics Olympiad Open Contest, organized by Indonesian Math Olympiad Team (Jan 2017)